Gunjan Tekade (1) Featured

Software Engineer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, PHP, React JS, JavaScript, jQuery, Ajax, HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, MySQL, PostgreSQL



Current Designation: Software Engineer Total Experience: 5 Year(s) 4 Month(s)

Current Company: DB XENTO SYSTEMS Notice Period: 2 Months

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computer Science and Current Location: Pune

Engineering]

Pref. Location: Pune

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Software Engineer, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Application

Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, PHP, React

JS, JavaScript, iQuery, Ajax, HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, MySQL, PostgreSQL

Verified: Email - id Phone Number |

Last Active: 18-Jan-21 Last Modified: 18-Jan-21

Summary

5 years of successful experience in the Web & Enterprise application development in JavaScript Technologies and Frameworks. Currently working as a Software Engineer at Xento Systems.

Good at problem identification and proposal of alternative solutions.

Quick learner and eager to learn new technologies.

Work Experience

DB XENTO SYSTEMS as Software Engineer

Feb 2017 to Till Date

Project : Accounts Payable (US Based) Technology: React JS, Fusebox, PostgreSQL

Description: The Accounts Payable is one of the products of the Property Management Software Application "Entrara". It provides the accounts payable process which handles company's all expenditures from vendor payments to employee expense reimbursements. There are multiple sub modules under this product and I have worked on some of them and those are Vendors, Invoices, Purchase Orders, Journal Entries, AP Payments, etc.

Duration : Feb 2017 to Jun 2018

: GL Accounting (US Based) Technology: React JS, Fusebox, PostgreSQL

Description: The GL Accounting is another one of the products of the Property Management Software Application "Entrara". Previously it was a part of Accounts Payable product, later on it got separated and has its own Product "GL Accounting". It handles all the GL book Accounting transactions and General Ledger setup parts. There are multiple sub modules under this product and I have worked on Journal Entries, GL Trees(General Ledger), Intercompany Invoices, Management fees etc.

: July 2017 to present Duration

SMARTFOX IT SOLUTIONS as Junior PHP Developer

Jun 2016 to Jan 2017

1/22/2021 https://freesearch.naukri.com/preview/printResume?uname=70355a918e836bc084af0b848a4961f95b545d52434501455215125c5a...

: VAHO Project

Technology : Codeigniter, JQuery, MySQL,
Description : It is an online food ordering system built for restaurants. I have independently done the development in this project and also used payment gateway for online payment process.

Project: TrademarkistPro

Technology : Codeigniter, JQuery, MySQL

: TrademarkistPro is an E-Filing Trademarks Application website, which enables online filling of trademarks Description

and provides online payment options using PayPal gateway.

Project : Thirann

Technology : Codeigniter, MySQL, JQuery

Description : It is an Online Course Enrollment website which offers multiple technical courses. The project has been

developed in Codeignator and also uses third party API integration.

PROMINENT SYSTEMS as Web Developer

May 2015 to Jun 2016

Project : Order Management System (OMS) Technology : Core PHP, MySQL, JavaScript

Description : OMS is an online Order Management System which takes orders by mobile application and

manages/process orders through web application.

Project : NEDAN

Technology : Core PHP, MySQL, JavaScript
Description : It is an Android application based Survey Management System. It takes surveys of multiple activities by

mobile application and manage/process through web application.

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computer Science and Engineering) from Nagpur Institute of Technology, Nagpur in 2014

IT Skills

Skill Name PHP	Version Last Used Experience
React Js, Javascript	
Jquery, Ajax	
HTML5, CSS	
BOOTSTRAP	
Fusebox, Codelgniter	
SMARTY	
Wind Smarty	
MYSQL, POSTGRESQL	
PhpStorm, WebStorm	
SVN, WAMP, XAMP	
Netbeans IDE, Filezilla	
APACHE	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak	
	•				

1/22/2021	https://freesearch.naukri.com/preview/printResume?uname=/0355a918e836bc084af0b848a4961f95b545d52434501455215125c5a		
English			
Hindi			
Marathi			

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time